Welcome, everyone, to TypeScript and View.
Excited to have you all here today as we dive right in.
So, to kick things off, a little bit about me.
So, a little fun fact, I really love going to your amusement park.
One of the nice things that's been great since the things that have started calming down
as far as pandemic and stuff is we can go back.
So, I've been to Universal Studios. This is not a recent photo,
but if you're looking for me, I'm the guy way in the back.
This is on the Universal Studio or Lando.
It's like park right where you just die like 80 feet.
It's an absolute blast.
So, if you ever get a chance,
be sure to check that out.
But the Universal Studio in LA,
they read it with the Jurassic World.
So, highly recommended if you're in the area.
So, check that out.
But, a fun fact's aside.
A little bit about me for those who don't aren't familiar with my work.
I'm a senior staff developer experience engineer at Nellify.
I'm on the View Core team, which is where some of you may know me from.
So, we'll do a lot of stuff in open source,
as well as a Nux Ambassador.
So, if you're not aware, there's also the Nuxary Workshop coming up in a couple of days.
So, if you want to learn about that,
be sure to join us for that as well.
I'll also teach on View Mastery,
and I'm also a Google Developer Expert.
It sounds like everyone here is
very excited to learn about the thing that I designed the workshop for,
which is getting you up and running with TypeScript and View,
because it's been kind of a tricky journey for View.
We'll talk a little bit about that,
but today we'll go through the internet and hopefully,
yeah, get a lot done.
All right, so as far as the workshop format for today,
basically when I teach workshops,
I follow these three principles as far as the recipe,
which is we start by learning the concept,
we question basically,
figure out what things really are,
so you all can ask questions,
and then we get to apply it,
and I think this is the key step.
So, just to kind of give some more examples,
when we're learning,
I'm going to be giving some explanations,
examples of how things actually work,
to can see that live.
Then of course, if anyone has any questions about what I just demoed,
or just needs to leave me the dive in a little bit deeper,
this is where we can do that.
And then as always with the workshops,
you get a chance to actually get a hands-on experience with it,
because after all,
how many of us have read books,
watch video courses,
and then when it comes to actually applying it,
it's an entirely separate matter.
So this entire course,
as we go through things,
you'll get lots of chances to be hands-on with the code.
So as much as humanly possible,
please try to actually do the exercises along with us.
We will be doing solutions,
so don't worry if you're feeling a little bit lost,
but yeah, that'll be a key part of the workshop.
And finally, as a reminder,
before we get started,
is that all code is compromised.
So a lot of things I'll be telling you about
are basically just things that I've observed.
They're not necessarily best practices
in terms of this is how you should always do things.
And so I encourage you to,
whether it's question or disagree with the things I'm saying,
because after all your opinion and experience matters,
and after at the end of the day,
you and your team are the one maintaining your code base,
and it's important to respect that at the end of the day.
Thank you very much.